and you want to find man a nice looking
working man am I right ladies what a
gorgeous handsome fine man like Denzel
Washington oh this L is gorgeous Denzel
is to women what Barney is to kids
[Applause]
Denzel walking here all the women go I
love you
[Laughter]
four or five months perfect gentleman
but around that fifth sixth month The
Jerk syndrome kicks in I tried to warn
my girlfriends I try to help them I'm
like ladies don't be fooled they pull
out the chair hold open the door whisper
sweet nothing's in your ear it's a setup
my same silly girlfriend
no anger
[Music]
I asked like all that stuff my man do
for me
I especially like when he be blowing in
my herb
what's the herb
you Airhead he was giving you a refill
that's why he was blowing in your ear
[Applause]
[Music]
love my girlfriend I do I love my
girlfriend but she's one of those people
who just cannot pronounce words properly
Now by round of applause be honest Round
of Applause how many of you know people
who just mess up the English Language by
round of applause
some of you are clapping if you don't
know somebody you are that somebody
just don't know it
my girlfriend same girlfriend she says
stuff like
my baby been going to school every day
he gonna get a perfect attendance to
stiff it
boo you need to go with him
girl I love some seafood
what is a swim it's like it's harder to
say it wrong right and she's always
leaving out important information she
was trying to tell me about one of her
other girlfriends brothers who left the
military they don't know where he is
girl
Trayvon that left the military
AOL
laughs
what are you saying he's lost on the
internet what do you mean come here come
here come here
[Laughter]
bless her little heart
that's the southern thing we say we
don't really want to offend you bless
your little heart
oh gosh tell you a little bit more about
me I have two children beautiful
children my son when he was born I
described him as the Gerber baby
I mean in every sense of the word I'm
talking blonde hair blue eyes cutest
little white boy you ever seen right my
son is albino I'm so cool with that
that's just how we were blessed
we're out in public get some strange
looks
people looking at me like I'm the nanny
oh yes mind your business ma'am you're
gonna get stabbed in the forehead yeah
have a great day
cool so cool but you know we're took him
to Disney World you tried taking a
toddler off the ride when the ride stops
you know how your children just show out
in public you know just fall out like
somebody just took every bone out of
their body like they've just been
filleted or something so son we've got
to go other people are waiting because
that's how I talk in public right other
people want to ride son Let's Go
laughs
so he falls out and we have to pick him
up and carry him out of the line we're
picking him up people are walking by
nosy people just walking by arms
flailing it's kicking his legs walking
by this one lady said poor thing he
probably just wants his mother
mind your business man you're going to
get stabbed in the forehead
have a great day have a great day oh my
son he's getting bigger now and so I I
go and check on him at night I can't say
I tuck him in I go check on him at night
and I was checking on him the other
night and
he said Mom what have you been eating
I don't know why why because your breath
stinks
whoa honest to a fault just like his mom
but just like his mom if he's offended
you we want to get it right right away
but Mom it's okay it's okay because at
school we're talking about dinosaurs and
every animal has a defense mechanism
your breath could be your defense
mechanism
Mom it's okay just like we don't even
need a gun somebody breaking the house
you just go
thanks son thanks
thanks now my daughter on the other hand
bubbling brown sugar feisty just like
her mom
she was born five weeks early at home on
the kitchen floor
I'm having labor pains I call my doctor
you know he says can you be here in an
hour sure doc I'll be there in an hour
my bag is already packed five weeks
early because I've got OCD right well
actually mine is CDO okay got my bag
packed come out of the bedroom take a
few steps
contraction hits me but I've been doing
Lamaze I can breathe through that I'm
breathing everything okay I'm good
take a few more steps I'm in the family
room another contraction hits me takes
me to the floor my water breaks I told
their father call it ambulance I'm not
gonna make it I'm not gonna make it this
genius that I'm married to or was
he looks in the phone book
I'm not making this up he looks in the
phone book I'm like what are you doing
it's 9-1-1 just call the ambulance and
so he's acting as if he's auditioning
for the bin Stein Visine commercial you
know that guy he's my wife is in labor
she says she's not gonna make it
I'm screaming will somebody just help me
so you can see my daughter moving down
the birth canal I'm now on the floor
will somebody help me help me her head
pops out he goes outside
to wait for the ambulance
I tell my son just go over there
somewhere you know you don't need to see
all of this just go over there I'm
screaming will somebody help me I hear
the ambulance I hear the siren then
somebody comes through the front door
runs through the living room runs
through the dining room runs through the
family room slides in home safe comes up
with the ball I mean baby in his hands
and I'm like it's a baby girl he said
but she's not crying this little woman
clears her throat
it was at that moment I realized I had
just given birth to The Other Woman
was my daughter
she has been feisty ever since she's a
tomboy just like I was any former
tomboys in the house yeah helps you
navigate in the world you're not so
scared right tomboy I was one of the
guys until I started liking the guy
now I'm showing up play tackle football
with lip gloss and eyeliner
hormones all over the place and the
fellas are looking at me like what's all
that stuff on your face
I'm like what stuff on my face
that was the secret weapon on my
brother's football team tackle football
they would pick me because no one ever
suspected that I could tackle and knock
you down I'd hit you low knock you flat
so I'm getting there right in front of
the center of the other team he's
getting ready to hike the ball I'm gonna
knock him flat like always
this time he hiked the ball the guy
knocks me flat
I'm on the ground my brother comes over
there yo man you picking up off my
sister I said no he's all right
[Laughter]
hormones all over
discussing a play
thank you for that thank you
laughs
I love my children but your people don't
raise children like I was raised back in
the day you know when Mama Said do
something you did it right it's What I
Call The Gospel According to Mama
I was in the grocery store and there was
a mother negotiating
with her son
I'm gonna count to three
and I'm thinking the only thing my mom
accounted were the minutes I was passed
out
after she beat me right
he wanted some Cocoa Puffs she's trying
to explain to him why he's gonna have
Life cereal he didn't want to hear that
popped it upside the head knocked the
cereal out of her hand
I'm like had that been my mama
only thing I heard in that store clean
up on all three
clean up one hour three Cocoa Puffs
would have been everywhere my mother
would take the cereal box and beat you
with it didn't I tell you but mama stop
you're a serial killer stop it
hahaha
as gas is
or how his milk is same as gas
oh my gosh
crazy crazy